# TAYLOR ST JEAN

- Personal information redacted for public copy of resume -

### PHYSICS AND ENGINEERING STUDENT

Currently studying at North Seattle College to obtain my Associate of Science degree. Relevant completed coursework includes Engineering Physics 221/222, Calculus I-III, Chemistry 161, and the full English Composition series. Plans after obtaining an AS include pursuing a Bachelor of Science degree at a four-year university, eventually acquiring a Doctorate in the field of physics. Limited working proficiency in French.

# **EDUCATION**

## NORTH SEATTLE COLLEGE

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE - IN PROGRESS

· Currently enrolled and actively studying to obtain my Associate of Science Track 2 degree, which is specifically designed for Physics and Engineering majors.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **BRN ENGINEERING**

INTERNSHIP · MAY 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

• The purpose of this position is to foster my talent in the field to better prepare me for similar jobs in the future. Topics covered include the pure engineering aspect of the job – operation of AutoCAD, production of building plans, the applications of various types of electrical equipment, etc. – as well as the code and business that accompanies it.

#### **ERA LIVING**

FOOD SERVER/HOST · DEC 2018 - PRESENT

• Duties include serving in the dining room during service, taking and filling orders and managing my time effectively to reduce wait times for the resident. As a host, I act as lead, assigning duties to all others working that night. Valuable skills I have learned on the job include communication with the blind and hard of hearing, the formation of interpersonal relationships, and effective communication with peers.

## SEATTLE FIRE DEPARTMENT

INTERNSHIP · JUL 2018 - Aug 2018

• This position was a six-week internship over the summer that covered firefighting and medical triage. I was trained in advanced CPR and first aid, wound treatment using various bandages, and how to respond in the event of a seizure or stroke. In addition, I was taught proper use of an extinguisher, basic fire science (flashpoint, fire type, etc.), and general fire prevention tactics.

## SKILLS

**Technical:** Microsoft Office/Excel, Linux, Python, Computer Hardware **Safety:** Fire Prevention and Response, Medical Triage, CPR/AED, First Aid

**STEM:** Physics, Circuitry, Mathematics, Basic Chemistry

	References/Project Portfolio available upon request	
--	---	--